Hello, everybody, and
welcome to
Episode 2 of
the Webdune Diaries.
Apologies if my
voice sounds
a little
bit off, I
was at a
rave on Saturday
so I'm feeling
a little bit
under the weather.
to talk a
bit about the
history of Webdune,
why I
made it
and where we're
up to.
What happened? A
friend and I,
Max and
I, we
had just finished
our degrees in
computer science at
University of Otago,
and we didn't
wanna work for,
a normal software
company as a
junior developer. We
were like, "We
like websites, they're
fun to build.
I've got some
design skills.
Max have got
some coding skills.
let's make some
websites and make
good money and
it'll all be
happy days and
we'll be able
to work out
of our bedrooms."
and five
years later,
it's kind
of true.
I'm working out
of a garage.
Look at that,
bikes and stuff.
the first year
and a half
was really tough.
I had worked,
from my parents'
house a little
bit, and then
was living with
friends for about
a year and
worked part time
as a courier
to pay rent
and survive, and
had a couple
projects, two or
three web projects,
during that period
of time and
some smaller pieces.
ended up
getting paid $2
an hour for
the first two
projects, which was
pretty tough and
that was based
on bad quoting
and just, like,
much more learning
than I expected.
and then after
that first year
and a half
of just battling
to survive
and learn,
I got a
job, a
contract with N4
Studio, they're now
a massive
web flow studio.
That's the tool
I often use
for websites. I
worked for them
for 18 months.
learning a lot
and making
some decent money,
which was cool.